<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on ISSEY SUKEDA</title>
    <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on ISSEY SUKEDA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/english/</guid>
      <description>I am a co-founder of EQUES Inc. . I love juggling and balloon art !
link to CV (preparing)
Research Interests Statistics (Copulas), Mathematical Optimization, Queueing Recognition, Medical AI
Preprint  Issey Sukeda, Atsushi Miyauchi, and Akiko Takeda: A study on modularity density maximization: Column generation acceleration and computational complexity analysis, arXiv:2206.10901.  Current Activities  Research Assistant at UTokyo MOCHA project Naminige project, Code for Japan  a digital hazardmap   For Earth  a student association to discuss SDGs   Ignite Your Ambition, Sony × UTokyo  Past Activities  2021 Entrepreneur Quest, UTokyo Matsuo Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/japanese/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/about/japanese/</guid>
      <description>情報理工学系研究科 数理情報学
株式会社EQUES Co-Founder/CTO
コピュラ統計学と数理最適化に興味を持っています. 医療AIの研究や待ち行列の研究などにも取り組んでいます.
趣味はジャグリング, バルーンアート, ギターなどです.
お知らせ  2022年10月 SenSys2022のPoster and Demoセッションで研究発表を行います. 2022年9月 日本オペレーションズ・リサーチ学会 秋季研究発表会にて研究発表を行いました. 2022年2月 学部の同期と, 株式会社EQUESを共同創業しました.  AI  JEESソフトバンクAI人材育成奨学生(令和4年度) 2022 Preferred Networks 2022~ 松尾研究所 2021~2022 ソニーコンピュータサイエンス研究所  学生時代の活動  なみにげ（デジタルハザードマップ開発プロジェクト） 東大社会起業コミュニティ For Earth 運営幹部HP 『美×音 うたをみる』運営幹部 HP Twitter  修了プログラム  松尾研究所起業クエスト 参加生 SHIBUYA QWS 4期生&amp;amp;5期生 チームkehai 本郷テックガレージ Summer Foundation Program ソニー東大社会連携講座 Ignite Your Ambition, TU Project 修了生 東大GLP-GEfIL 修了生 東大トライリンガルプログラム 前期課程修了生 UTSIP(UTokyo Summer Internship Program) @ 東大森田研究室  受賞  Finalist, FinSUM Business Contest 2021 link Yahoo Prize, Civictech Challenge Cup 2021 U-22 link First place, AI/SUM Business Contest 2020 link Second place, UTokyo MDS Data Analysis Contest 2019 link Third place, All Japan Diabolo Competition Bronze Award, Chemistry Grand Prix link  出演・掲載  Malabaristas 27th 卒業記念動画 YouTube 五月祭2021 YouTube 駒場祭2020 Malabari Express 999 YouTube 文化祭2016 YouTube 文化祭2015 中夜祭 YouTube U-23サミット2020 学生登壇 東大新聞「学生生活紹介」 link マスフェスタ（高校）  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
