<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on ISSEY SUKEDA</title>
    <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on ISSEY SUKEDA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 13:54:18 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Competition</title>
      <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 13:54:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/competition/</guid>
      <description>統計データ分析系のコンテスト一覧  総務省統計データ分析コンテスト  データセット：   MDSデータサイエンスコンテスト  データセット:   10 スポーツデータサイエンスコンペティション   常時開催  Kaggle SIGNATE  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookmark</title>
      <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/bookmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/bookmark/</guid>
      <description>コピュラ統計学 コピュラ一般  基本的な内容(IBIS 2009より) 極値での従属性および非対称性と信用ポートフォリオリスク(吉羽先生,2021) Copulas with Maximum Entropy(Piantadosi et al.)  チェスコピュラに対するエントロピー最大化   Maximum entropy distribution of order statistics with given marginals (Bernoulli 2018)  周辺分布を固定しエントロピー最大化. multidiagonalsの問題に帰着.   Bivariate distributions with ordered marginals Relationship Between Kendall’s tau Correlation and Mutual Information  Extreme Copula  A New Estimator for the Pickands Dependence Function extreme copulaの密度関数 link Kamnitui et al.  緩和extreme copulaのうちτを固定した下で選べる範囲の解析    コピュラエントロピーに関する研究  Multivariate Normality Test with Copula Entropy 著者:Jian Ma copent: Estimating Copula Entropy and Transfer Entropy in R  copula entropyの推定手法.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stardust-coder.github.io/myportfolio/page/publication/</guid>
      <description>論文  (共著, MobiHoc&#39;22)MOCHA: Mobile Check-in Application for University Campuses Beyond COVID-19 Issey Sukeda, Atsushi Miyauchi, and Akiko Takeda: A study on modularity density maximization: Column generation acceleration and computational complexity analysis, Preprint, arXiv:2206.10901.  学会発表  Recursive Queueing Estimation Using Smartphone-based Acoustic Ranging, SenSys2022(予定) International Workshop on Continuous Optimization 日本オペレーションズ・リサーチ学会 秋季研究発表会 最適化手法とアルゴリズム ─未来を担う若手研究者の集い 2022─ HP  その他  Preferred Networks テックブログ寄稿  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
